And now we're going to talk about some inputs that you can run through your board.
Here we have the Denon DNC635 CD player.
Has many features.
Some of which aren't fantastically useful.
Let's play some music here.
OK.
So it has your basic CD player features.
Stop, obviously, duh.
Play, woohoo.
And you know Pause, no surprise there.
Important things you need to know about the Denon player is when you want to change tracks you use this button that's called Push, and you turn it sideways.
Don't push it, turn it sideways.
And you can see the track numbers is advancing.
One, two, three.
OK?
So there we go.
That's how you change tracks.
And when you're ready to play, hit play, obviously.
Now a great feature of the Denon CD player is, if you decide this is the track you want, instead of hitting pause, which just pauses it, or hitting stop, which actually would bring you back to track one, you can hit, go find the track you want again, track three in this case.
Hit play.
Yes that's what I want.
And then you hit the Cue button and what that does is, is it brings you back to the beginning of track three.
So find your track with the, turning this button that says Push on it, paradoxically.
And then use Cue to go to the beginning of the track you want to play.